A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Go eat all you can then eat more and more eat as much as you need to consume everything
in your path until you become the ultimate evil.
You are...
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか?
六人目も合わさず運命まで絡んでく
行き先もらったポテル食えない夜の端で
不可愛しすぎた眩しさが悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか?
出会ったわけは途絶びに引き付けられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
キトラフィールド
の화 влад
アドライ over
空のページ
お寿命だ
We didn't come here to be tourists or to stuff our faces.
Do you get that, Sol?
No, we're in Italy for an extracurricular lesson, okay?
Yeah, I do know that, Maka.
You didn't have to scramble my freaking brains.
Our target this time is some murderer named Sansan J, isn't it?
So you were paying attention.
Of course. This guy likes to lay low until after dark, right?
Nice try, but we're not sightseeing right now.
We have to gather more information about the city.
Ugh, fine.
That's better. Let's see.
Where can we go to find some information?
Oh, sorry.
Hey, hold it, punk.
Problem?
You bet there is. I got a problem with any punk who runs into me like that.
Who do you think you're messing with? Maybe you'd like me to show you, huh?
If you spoke more and spit less, maybe I'd be able to understand you.
What did Small Fry say?
No problem. If you don't understand, we'll explain it to you.
Do you know who controls this town? The Materazzi. That's who. And don't you forget it.
I couldn't care less about that if I tried.
So quit messing around with these guys. We've got work to do.
Yeah, fine by me.
I don't think so. You're not going anywhere.
Huh?
If you think you can cross the Materazzi and get away with it, you're stupider than you look.
We'll show you what happens to punks.
Let him have it.
I wonder where we should go to get some information.
Good question. We could try that smoke shop that's around the corner.
Black-blooded terror. There's a weapon inside Krona?
No.
Hey!
Go and eat your food.
You are the ultimate creation.
You are perfect weapon and meister together in one form.
Hey, what's your deal, pink hair?
Eat their souls. All of their souls.
No, I can't. I'm not ready to do it yet.
Get her.
Hey, you. Did you hear me?
They're not Kishin. Not anywhere close to it.
You listening? I said what's your deal.
Yeah, freaking. Who are you talking to anyway?
Snake, snake. Cobra, cobra.
It will be all right. Have faith in yourself.
Crona, you will be a Kishin.
I am a Kishin.
Don't make the mistake of thinking you could just walk into our castle uninvited and walk out again, you dirty punk.
This is a public place, actually. The castle doesn't belong exclusively to you or to anyone else for that matter. Which is why Ragnarok is going to eat you all. Right now.
What's up with that car? It's too loud!
Hey, everybody. I feel like something amusing is happening. The doors here open only one way. They open inward.
The thing yesterday sure was fun, wasn't it?
I don't remember what it was, though.
Well, no matter.
This much I know. My blood is black.
Found him. Finally.
More power. More soul.
Listen, you murderous maniac. Sonson J, your soul is mine now. It's over.
That's the last one we need to collect on this trip, right?
Yeah. And swallowing this soul is going to be cooler than all you can eat pasta.
I was wondering, do souls taste good? You seem to like them.
Yeah, they're delicious. They don't really have a particular flavor. It's just the way they feel going down, the texture.
Hmm. So how do you think Blackstar and Tsubaki are doing? I wonder if they're having any more luck collecting souls than usual.
I doubt it. They're professional losers when it comes to soul collecting. Permanent zeros.
You feel bad for poor Tsubaki.
Blackstar's energy isn't directed at soul collecting. He's more interested in puffing up his own ego.
Anyway, we're done here. Let's go. You can wait down below for me. I'll go get the bike and bring it around.
Hey, soul. Hold on.
Hmm? Why? Something wrong?
That building.
I seem to remember someone saying we didn't come here to sightsee. Oh, that was you.
It's not that. Something else. I sense something. A group of souls all wound up together over there.
It's all so noisy. Concentrate. Harder.
They're all in that building I pointed to. I can sense the souls of a weapon and a meister. And then there are 50 or 60 human souls surrounding them.
Wow. You can tell all that from over here?
Yeah. It surprised me, too. I think it looks like the humans in there are those guys from this afternoon.
Oh, those idiots again? Why do we care what happens to them?
I don't like them any more than you do, soul. But they're still human. They're punks, but it's not like their souls have become quiche and eggs.
Let's just forget about them, Maka. It's Saturday night, after all. For all we know, maybe they've just got a little fever going on.
No, soul. Now's not the time for jokes. We're representatives of the academy. If we ignore it and something bad happens, it'll be too late.
Okay, okay. You win. We'll check it out.
But if we storm in there and it ends up being a bunch of people with Blackstar in the center saying,
Welcome to my big show, I'm gonna cry.
I only hope that's all it is.
Here we are. Looks like we get to do some sightseeing after all. I do love Gothic architecture. This is one cool building.
Oh, no! Impossible!
Hey, what's wrong?
There's no way. Not that quickly.
Okay, slow down a second. Take a breath. When you start acting like this, I can't keep up with you.
All gone.
What? The bell? Yeah, it stopped.
No, no. I'm talking about the human souls that were inside. They disappeared suddenly.
Now there's just the weapon and the Meister. Something tells me that we should leave this door closed and get out of here.
But I can't. I have to know. As a student of the academy, it's my duty to find out what happened.
You see? They open one way. Those doors only open inward.
What the hell? He's in there all by himself. What happened to his weapon partner?
No, there's no way.
Now what?
Lady Medusa, it looks like two others have arrived.
Keep it down, Ragnarok. You need to be quiet now.
I'm reading the souls of a Meister and a weapon. And both of them are directly in front of us. Which means...
That Meister standing there... has a weapon inside his body.
I screwed up.
Oh, yeah. Maka isn't even at school right now. All this risk for nothing. The only place to see Maka is here at the academy, so I came. Sure. But coming here means I might run into him.
Frankenstein! All I wanted was to see my daughter. Instead, I'm staring straight in the face of danger.
But don't worry, Maka. Your papa's not going to back down. I will overcome this obstacle. And when I do, you'll know how much I love you. You'll finally understand!
But before I do all that, I need to have the lovely school nurse heal my wounded heart and give me courage. Oh, yes.
I've been waiting for you, my angel. Hurry now and heal my heart with your sweet, sweet medical love and kiss my pain away.
Hey, there, spirit. I've been looking for you.
Ah-ah! The Stein!
I don't know what you want with me, but all the scars from your experiments have finally disappeared!
I'm not afraid of you anymore, so there! I'm not afraid of anything. How do you like that, Stein?
Then, I take it you noticed that I swapped the middle toe from your right foot with the one on your left foot?
Ah! What are you nuts?! How could you do something like that to me?!
Made you look!
You know, that little daughter of yours, Maka? She's growing up quickly, huh?
I have to be honest. When I heard you were getting married, I wasn't so sure about it.
I thought to myself, there's no way this is going to work out.
But then, I watched the two of you together, and you seemed so close that I was reassured.
And then, I thought, those two have found a love that is sure to last forever.
Um, yeah, about that. You may not know this yet, but Maka's mother and I, we actually got divorced last month.
It's over between us.
I know.
Damn it! I'm gonna kill you, you heartless, backward freak!
Oh, yeah, one other thing.
It seems the demon sword has turned up.
What?
What are you talking about, Maka?
You're telling me there's a weapon inside that dude?
Not for long. It's coming out.
What?
Here we go.
It's so cool,
you dollyettes!
Who?
Where did I go?
And I'm going to jump inside!
C'mon!
poking
the
That hurts me.
It hurts. It hurts. It hurts.
Stop moving around like that. You're squeezing me.
Don't help me. Ow, stum already.
Don't push my nose.
You're squeezing me.
Stop it now. I've had enough already.
Now, now, calm down, Krona.
You're so scary when you're stressed out like this.
Okay, this is getting weird.
You should know that the hunting of human souls is strictly forbidden.
Are you students?
I haven't seen you at the academy.
At the where? What academy?
Anyway, she said it was okay to eat the human souls.
I don't see what's wrong with it if she said it was okay.
I'm not very good at talking to girls.
They make me nervous.
Never mind that. Her soul looks tasty.
Meisters and their weapons are not allowed to collect human souls for any reason.
We hunt only the souls that have become Kishan eggs.
Now it's my duty to stop you.
You will not hunt any more humans. You hear me?
Let's get her, Krona.
It turned into a weapon.
A sword.
He's gonna strike from below.
Stop this!
You're going to start poking at me also.
You've got him now!
AHHHHH!
Did you think you could cut him in half?
Oh no. Not with a stroke like that one.
Black? Black blood?
Yes. That's right. My blood is black.
What's up with this guy? His body's way freaky.
I think I have an idea.
I don't know how it's possible, but I think his blood itself is a weapon.
I was able to cut through his skin, but his blood hardened and the blade stopped completely when I hit his blood vessels.
Well, if you're right, then how do you propose we go about beating him?
None of our normal attacks will work.
I'm not even sure which hunter will help.
If only I could shoot my soul wavelength directly at him like Blackstar does, I might be able to do some internal damage.
Otherwise, I have no idea what to do.
Krona, why are you taking it so easy?
Do something.
It's not like the ones before. Those were boys.
She's a girl. I'm no good with girls.
What am I supposed to do with her?
How silly.
Kill her, of course.
What's with this guy? And who is he talking to anyway?
Oh, okay. You're saying I can kill the girl?
I didn't realize that.
But maybe I could play with her hair first.
Just for a little while.
The doors here open inward.
They only open one way.
Ragnarok.
Screaming resonance.
Go beat.
It's coming, Maka. Guard now.
Ragnarok.
Soul! Stop it!
Are you okay, soul? Talk to me.
You don't need to worry about that right now.
I am your weapon partner, Maka.
That means I am always prepared to die for my maister.
What do I do now?
That screaming causes vibrations along his blade,
and his blood hardens so quickly.
I can't do any damage to him at all.
I can't even guard.
I screwed up.
What's the matter, Maka?
Quit dodging and start fighting back!
Maka!
But if I do attack,
then soul...
I can't use soul to block his sword.
The only thing I can do now is run away.
We're getting out of here!
Open up!
That's not going to work, you know.
We should start paying attention to the things other people say.
Oh, no.
The doors here only open one way.
They open inward.
Maka! Stop him now!
But soul, if I guard you'll die!
I screwed up.
Let's go!
Oh
So so do all girls shout this much
Please open your eyes
Listen to me the doors here only open one way they open inward
I'm sorry if I wasn't so weak then this wouldn't have happened
I don't usually listen to how people talk. I don't think I can deal with the situation on
The next episode of soul eater medusa the witch the one who possesses a great evil soul
I don't know how to deal with any of this